// For the answer value, please use the letter of the correct answer
module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'what color was tweety bird when he was first created?',
	a: 'yellow',
	b: 'pink',
	c: 'black and white',
	d: 'blue',
	answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'which body part always gets blown off of daffy duck?',
	a: 'his head',
	b: 'his eyes',
	c: 'his beak',
	d: 'his tail',
	answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'which looney tunes character speaks with a stutter?',
	a: 'porky the pig',
	b: 'bugs bunny',
	c: 'yosemite sam',
	d: 'daffy duck',
	answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'who was the very first looney tunes character?',
	a: 'speedy gonzales',
	b: 'bugs bunny',
	c: 'porky pig',
	d: 'bosko',
	answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'who is wiley coyote always trying to catch?',
	a: 'bugs bunny',
	b: 'road runner',
	c: 'tweety bird',
	d: 'tasmanian devil',
	answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'what kind of pet does marvin the martian have?',
	a: 'dog',
	b: 'cat',
	c: 'rock',
	d: 'an R2D2 unit',
	answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'what is TAZ known for?',
	a: 'eating cookies all the time',
	b: 'moving around like a tornado',
	c: 'pouncing on people',
	d: 'slobbering on everything',
	answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'what phrase is sylvester famous for saying?',
	a: 'thuffering thuccotash',
	b: 'shh be vewy vewy quiet',
	c: 'meep meep',
	d: 'eh whats up doc',
	answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'what phrase is elmer fudd most known for?',
	a: 'vive l\'amour',
	b: 'i twat i saw a puddy tat',
	c: 'th-th-thats all folks',
	d: 'shh be vewy vewy quiet',
	answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'what phrase is bugs bunny most known for?',
	a: 'eh whats up doc',
	b: 'i twat i saw a puddy tat',
	c: 'th-th-thats all folks',
	d: 'shh be vewy vewy quiet',
	answer: 'a'
  }
]

